Privacy Policy
==============

Last updated: June 21, 2021

This Privacy Policy describes Our policies and procedures on the collection, use and disclosure of Your information when You use the Service and tells You about Your privacy rights and how the law protects You.

Interpretations and Definitions
-------------------------------

The words of which the initial letter is capitalized have meanings defined under the following conditions. The following definitions shall have the same meaning regardless of whether they appear in singular or in plural.

### Definitions

For the purposes of this Privacy Policy:

* Account means a unique account created for You to access our Service or parts of our Service.
* Affiliate means an entity that controls, is controlled by or is under common control with a party, where "control" means ownership of 50% or more of the shares, equity interest or other securities entitled to vote for election of directors or other managing authority.
* Application means the software program provided by the Company downloaded by You on any electronic device, named Ninja VPN.
* Company (referred to as either "the Company", "We", "Us" or "Our" in this Agreement) refers to Ninja VPN.
* Country refers to: Estonia  
    
* Device means any device that can access the Service such as a computer, a cell phone or a digital tablet.
* Personal Data is any information that relates to an identified or identifiable individual.
* Service refers to the Application.
* Service Provider means any natural or legal person who processes the data on behalf of the Company. It refers to third-party companies or individuals employed by the Company to facilitate the Service, to provide the Service on behalf of the Company, to perform services related to the Service or to assist the Company in analyzing how the Service is used.
* You means the individual accessing or using the Service, or the company, or other legal entity on behalf of which such individual is accessing or using the Service, as applicable.

Data Collection and Children's Privacy
--------------------------------------

Our Service does not collect personally identifiable information from You.

Our Service does not address anyone under the age of 13 and does not collect personally identifiable information from anyone under the age of 13.

User Responsibility
-------------------

You are entirely responsible for all the content you upload while using Our Service.

Links to Other Websites
-----------------------

Our Service may contain links to other websites that are not operated by Us. If You click on a third party link, You will be directed to that third party's site. We strongly advise You to review the Privacy Policy of every site You visit.

We have no control over and assume no responsibility for the content, privacy policies or practices of any third party sites or services.

Changes to this Privacy Policy
------------------------------

We may update Our Privacy Policy from time to time. We will notify You of any changes by posting the new Privacy Policy on this page.

We will let You know via email and/or a prominent notice on Our Service, prior to the change becoming effective and update the "Last updated" date at the top of this Privacy Policy.

You are advised to review this Privacy Policy periodically for any changes. Changes to this Privacy Policy are effective when they are posted on this page.

Contact Us
----------

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, You can contact us:

* By visiting this page on our website: [](https://ninjavpn.io/privacy/)https://ninjavpn.io/privacy/
* By email: NinjaVPN, Padriku tee 12/3-4, Tallinn, Estonia
